Oh, no.
Zhiyan,
I'll be right back.
Your Highness, please spare me.
I...
I really don't know where the princess consort went.
I saw the princess consort fall asleep last night,
then I left.
When I came to wake her up just now,
I found
she was gone.
Don't think I don't know
what tricks you are playing.
You'd better be honest.
Otherwise, you'll be punished.
You guys go find the princess consort.
If you can't find her,
don't come back.
Yes.
What are you doing here?
Do you need me to teach you how to find her?
Go!
Butterfly.
Where is the butterfly?
Shen Suhe.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
I can't find the butterfly.
What are you doing?
Butterfly?
Princess consort.
It's princess consort.
Princess consort, you're back.
You ran out without telling me.
Why didn't you tell me?
You can't sneak out anymore.
Do you know?
There are bad people outside.
Bad people who eat people.
But
my butterfly is missing.
I... I need to find it.
Where is it?
Princess,
let me take you back to freshen up first.
Then we can go catch butterflies together.
Okay?
Can we still find it?
Yes.
Alright then.
This is the Prime Minister's Residence.
The Prime Minister's Residence.
Thank you, Mr. Shen,
for saving me.
No need to thank me.
It was my sister who insisted on bringing you back to heal.
It seems you know it was she who brought you back.
Then I assume
you must know her background.
Forgive me for speaking frankly.
the wounds on your body
are mostly caused by sharp blades.
And the palms of your hands
are calloused.
You
are definitely not an ordinary person.
My sister grew up in the Prime Minister's Residence.
She is kind-hearted
and naive.
She and you
are not the same kind.
Mr. Shen, rest assured,
I only
met your sister a few times.
We're not close.
We won't
meet much in the future.
That's good.
In the entire mansion,
only I know you're here to heal.
So I can't
let you stay over.
Thank you.
I hope you keep your promise
and stop bothering my sister.
This is from Sui'er.
Breakfast is ready.
The servants have been dismissed.
After you eat,
you can leave on your own.
Sui'er.
Isn't this General Defending the State?
Haven't you heard?
General Xiao used to be invincible.
But recently, in a battle,
his entire army was wiped out.
He was even missing for a while.
In my opinion,
he must have defected to the enemy.
Yeah.
Why did you tear it?
I've served the empire for years,
and I've never been disloyal.
But I was slandered
just because of a defeat.
I must go to the Emperor
to explain it clearly.
Qianzhi,
now that you know there's someone behind it,
you should know
this is just to lure you out.
Don't be impulsive.
Settle down first,
then we'll make a plan.
Prince Yu,
we've been together on the border for years.
You should know my character.
I'm not afraid of tens of thousands of enemies.
How could I be afraid of a treacherous villain?
If I hide here,
and live a precarious life,
where should those soldiers
who fought with me go?
Can I just watch them
bear this false accusation because of me?
Brother,
you know I didn't mean that.
The enemy hasn't shown up yet.
It's the best choice
to stay put.
When I know who's behind it,
we'll crush them all at once.
Although
His Majesty is suspicious,
he's not stupid.
Without concrete evidence,
he won't jump to conclusions.
My brother, think back,
is there any evidence
that might be in someone else's hands?
Now that you mention it,
there is indeed something fishy.
On that day of defeat,
I was captured by the enemy.
I endured torture day and night.
Later, I managed to escape.
But I can't recall
what happened during those days.
I vaguely remember
they forced me
to sign something.
You have experienced hundreds of battles.
How can ordinary torture
harm you?
They must have used some special means.
It's taro powder.
Your Highness, do you remember
the acupuncture kit you gave me some time ago?
This morning,
Dr. Xue sent a message back,
saying that the silver needles
were all poisoned,
named Taro powder,
produced in the West Shu,
which can be used to anesthetize the senses,
and also used in witchcraft to hallucinate people.
Every year, the West Shu
will make a small tribute to the palace.
Based on General Xiao's statement,
it's very likely that he was poisoned.
Taro powder?
Could the mastermind
be the Second Prince?
I have never met him before,
and hold no grudges against him.
Why would the Second Prince
frame me?
I remember that you
were close to Prime Minister Shen,
and occasionally exchange letters.
That was many years ago.
Why do you ask?
We have been fighting at the border for a long time,
and are not familiar with the court affairs.
Do you know that the Second Prince
and Prime Minister Shen are arch-enemies at the court?
He is not targeting you,
but using you
as a pawn to bring down Prime Minister Shen.
By the way,
I also found
a pharmaceutical factory
named "Great Apricot Pharmacy" in the city.
It seems to have secretly developed this poison.
The owner of this pharmacy
is a counselor of the Second Prince.
Miss,
what's in this letter?
The poison
is indeed made by Mu Jinghao.
I need to get out of here.
The Second Prince ordered that
you can't leave the mansion.
How can you get out?
He sent this secret letter to me,
which means
this mansion
is not completely sealed off.
Zhiyan.
Have you
seen a golden hairpin
a golden hairpin around here?
That's the princess consort's most precious hairpin.
She hasn't left the mansion these days.
It must be in this yard.
You guys,
hurry up and find it!
His Highness instructed us before leaving
to stay here and guard this place.
I've told you,
that hairpin
must be in some corner of this mansion.
You know
the princess consort's temper.
If she starts making a fuss
because we can't find that hairpin,
don't blame me for not warning you.
Where could it have fallen?
Zhiyan,
do you know what that hairpin looks like?
About this long,
with a crabapple blossom on the end.
I remember the princess consort played there before.
You go there to find it.
Go!
Look carefully.
Don't miss any corners.
Miss
Can we do this?
Cut the crap.
Squat down.
Can we really do this?
Come on.
What's going on?
I found it.
Here it is.
Go ahead.
Go.
Prince Rui's Mansion is heavily guarded.
Not even a fly can get out.
I thought the princess consort wouldn't show up.
I have my way.
Don't bother.
Can you act?
I'm sure I'm not worse than you.
Sir,
what medicine do you want?
What illness do you want to cure?
My Lord has no other hobbies,
but loves to study pharmacology,
especially some rare and strange medicines.
I don't think your shop is big enough.
I don't know if you can find what we want.
Look at you.
Our shop
is small,
but it's well-equipped.
If we don't have the medicine,
then the entire Kyoto,
including the imperial palace, can't find it.
Really?
Then take a look,
do you have
do you have them?
May I ask
what these herbs are for?
Many of these herbs
aren't even native to the Grand Commandant.
I've already said,
our master loves studying herbal medicine.
Would he bother coming here
for ordinary herbs?
If you have them,
I'm willing to pay double.
But if
you dare to lie to me,
I'll make you
pay back a hundred times.
You're joking.
We never dare to
sell fake medicine.
Please wait a moment.
I'll ask the owner.
What a coincidence!
We just received
a batch of herbs recently.
The ones you're looking for
are all included.
But these herbs
aren't usually in demand,
so they're stored in the herb repository.
Please follow me.
You two,
wait a moment.
Take a look,
is this the herb you're looking for?
Looks like we're in the right place.
Pack all of these for us.
No problem.
I think
you must have
some rare treasures here.
Would it be
possible for us to take a look inside?
I'm sorry,
but these herbs have strict storage requirements.
We don't
allow outsiders to get close,
let alone let you in.
If the owner finds out,
I'll be in trouble.
How would you be in trouble?
We'll just be in there for a while.
It won't take long.
We'll be out soon.
I... this morning,
I might have eaten something bad.
Please wait for me a moment.
Hurry up.
Young Master,
there are indeed many rare treasures here.
How about
we buy some to take back?
No need to shout.
The people have already left.
Hurry up and look.